Rodrigo Muniz

FullStack Developer / Front-End Developer

ABOUT

FullStack developer | Front-End Developer | Angular Developer | React | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | And some technologies in back too (C# | Node), it's almost 20 years of experience as a developer, I love working as front-end developer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

AVANADE | 12/2020

- Development of application according to specifications.
- · Development of front-end applications in Angular, JavaScript and Wordpress.
- Maintenance/Update of Stored Procedures of Oracle and SQL Server Databases.
- · Modification of some routines in the system in C#.

DEVELOPER / ANALYST

CAPTA TECNOLOGIA | 05/2019 - 12/2020

- · Development of application according to specifications.
- · Development of web and desktop applications.

TEAM COORDINATOR

SUPPREMO HOSPITALITY (New Zealand) | 03/2018 - 07/2018

- Responsible for organizing professional activity schedules for events.
- Experience in coordinating the work of professionals at events and monitoring quality.
- Experience in preparing/separating material and labor for events.

MANAGER / ADMINISTRATOR

NOSSA CLINICA | 05/2015 - 09/2017

- · Responsible for hiring a team of clinic professionals and doctors.
- · Controlled and managed the clinic's financial accounts.
- Maintained upwards improvements to the clinic in order to increase profitability and reduce costs.
- Managed the staff of 35 doctors and 25 others.

CONTACT

Phone: 11 94906-4582 e-mail: ramunizbh@yahoo.com.br Skype: ramunizbh@yahoo.com.br

SOCIAL MEDIA

fb:www.facebook.com/ramunizbh li:www.linkedin.com/in/rodrigoam uniz

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MANAGER / ADMINISTRATOR

VAN EXPRESSO | 01/2014 - 05/2015

- Responsible for the administration and management of the company and the activities and tasks for the employees.
- · Implemented the work structure systems.
- Development and maintenance of the web site and Google's ad-words advertisement.
- · Responsible for advertisement and search of clients.

DEVELOPER / ANALYST

BDK SOLUTIONS | 06/2012 - 10/2013

- Surveyed and made specifications of requirements with the end user, designing processes and information flow for the development of systems.
- · Developed applications according to specifications.
- Study in economic-financial real estate feasibility for development and specification of the changes in the system.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

CSS - Advanced PhotoShop - Advanced CorelDraw - Advanced Visual Basic - Advanced Java - Intermediary HTML - Advanced Java Script - Advanced PHP - Advanced C++ - Intermediary ASP - Intermediary Visual FoxPro - Advanced SQL Developer - Advanced Oracle/Oracle Dev - Advanced MS-SQL Server - Advanced Access - Advanced MySQL - Intermediary Windows - Advanced Bootstrap - Intermediary JQuery - Intermediary Angular - Advanced React - Advanced

LANGUAGES

English – Advanced Portuguese - Native

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Web Developer Ironhack – Jul 2020 – Dez 2020

Postgraduate in Project Management FDC (BH) | 2008 – 2009

Web Management Technologist UNI BH(BH) | 2004 – 2006

COURSES

- PREPARATION FOR IELTS(English proficiency)
 DynaSpeak New Zeland (02/2018 07/2018)
- LEADERSHIP AND TEAM MANAGEMENT Udemy – 06/2018
- COACHING TRAINING IPC, 10/2017
- Advanced Trading DN2 Business (BH), 05/2010